eatz.com 2019-06-01

# Privacy Policy | Eatz

eatz.com value the trust you place in [https://www.eatz.com](https://www.eatz.com/). This statement discloses the information practices for the eatz.com, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used and with whom the information is shared. 

### Collection of Personally Identifiable Information

eatz.com collects your personal information for the purpose of site security and to ensure our service remains available to all users. The personal information we collect from you will include information you give us when you:

  * Contact us
  * Complete a transaction with us

eatz.com will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Use of 'Cookies':

eatz.com may set and access eatz.com cookies on your computer in order to track you when you're on our websites and to recognize your visits. eatz.com may use web beacons to access eatz.com cookies inside and outside of our network of websites and in connection with eatz.com services.

### Security Precautions:

We endeavor to take all security measures to protect your personal information. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

### Other Websites:

Our website may have links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website. You should therefore read the privacy policies of the other websites when you are using those sites.
